// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Choose correct Alphabetical order for words \"Apple, Crayon, Ball, Dog\" ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "Apple, Ball, Crayon, Dog",
    options: [
      "Dog, Apple, Ball, Crayon",
      "Ball, Apple, Crayon, Dog",
      "Apple, Crayon, Ball, Dog",
      "Apple, Ball, Crayon, Dog"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Choose correct Alphabetical order for words \"watch, worm, when, wild\" ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "watch, when, wild, worm",
    options: [
      "watch, when, wild, worm",
      "watch, worm, when, wild",
      "worm, wild, when, watch",
      "when, wild, watch, worm"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Choose correct Alphabetical order for words \"paper, rose, bat, cat\" ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "bat, cat, paper, rose",
    options: [
      "rose, cat, bat, paper",
      "bat, cat, paper, rose",
      "rose, paper, cat, bat",
      "paper, rose, bat, cat"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which word from the options comes first alphabetically.",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "olive",
    options: [
      "X-ray",
      "olive",
      "zebra",
      "queen"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which word from the options comes first alphabetically.",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "pace",
    options: [
      "pan",
      "paper",
      "party",
      "pace"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which word from the options comes last alphabetically.",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "raccoon",
    options: [
      "raccoon",
      "mouse",
      "airplane",
      "igloo"
    ]
  }
  ,
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which word from the options comes last alphabetically.",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "good",
    options: [
      "gate",
      "goat",
      "good",
      "goal"
    ]
  }
  /*
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A boy had total 50 pens. He gave equal pens among 10 friends, How many pens each friend get?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "6",
      "4",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "There are total 20 soaps and packets comes with 4 soaps per packet. How many such packets will be there?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
        "5",
        "6",
        "4",
        "3"
      ]
  },
  /*
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: " 9 * 9 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "81",
    options: [
      "18",
      "88",
      "17",
      "81"
    ]
  }
  */
];
